Fatih Ozdemir

Mobile phone: 0404 311 986 Email: Fatihzdmr-08@hotmail.com

License: Vic Full Driver's License

Objective:

To further my experience and be exposed to the various fields in the surveying industry expanding my knowledge gained from the almost complete Bachelor of Applied science (Land Surveying) at RMIT University. In the long-term, after having the privilege to experience the many tasks in surveying, I aim to be a Licensed Surveyor once I feel confident. Every opportunity given will be a chapter to my end goal.

Education:

- Bachelor of Applied science (surveying) at RMIT University (2020-
- Advanced diploma of surveying at RMIT University (Completed Nov 2019)
- **Diploma** of Surveying at RMIT University (Completed Nov 2018)
- Completion of YEAR 12 **VCE** studies at Roxburgh college (2017)

Other training:

- Level two first aid certificate & CPR (08/2021)
- C.I white card
- Manual handling in the Workplace certificate @ AVELING (07/2021)
- Drug and Alcohol Awareness certificate @ AVELING (07/2021)
- Implement Traffic Management Plans @ Edway Training (07/2021)

Employment History:

Heading & Associates (Kensington) – Survey Assistant (2018 – work experience) (05/2022-)

- Using Leica TS16 local station & Leica Viva GS16 GPS
- Re-establishment, feature, and level surveys in residential areas Cadastral Surveying
- Building line setouts

MNG Land Surveyors – Survey Technician (2021-2022)

- Leica TS16 and Leica GS18
- Subdivision surveying, AsCons, Dspecs & sewer pick ups

Calibre Group (Southbank) Engineering & surveying – Survey assistant (2019-2021)

- Using Trimble S6 Total station and Trimble GPS rover (R2)
- Subdivision surveying Title pegging
- Re-establishment, feature & level surveys Greenfield
- AsCons, Dspecs, Rspecs & sewer surveys

Digaway Group - Labourer (2017-2019)

- Landscaping
- Manual handling and labour
- Spotter (trench)

Delcon Projects - Carpentry (2016-2017)

- Timber cuts
- assist in setting out a house (carpentry)
- Manual handling and labour

Availability:

Monday	Tuesday	Wednesday	Thursday	Friday	Saturday	Sunday
N/A due to study commitments	N/A due to study commitments	N/A due to study commitments	Available	Available	Available	Available

Interests:

- Sports- AFL, Soccer, Cricket, Basketball and Tennis.
- History & Geography Facts
- Fitness & health Nutrition, Physical education
- Mathematics

Referees:

Toby Manning

Senior educator – Surveying and property services

Tel: 9925 4934 Email: toby.manning@rmit.edu.au

Mohamed Zahlan

Surveyor – Calibregroup

Tel: 0404026359